SARA WAGNER

Profile

A passionate and devoted professional with an eagerness to create innovative and brilliant web experiences. Reliable and friendly, able to work with little oversight and collaborate in team environments. Exceptional interpersonal skills with efficient and effective communication. Flexible in job functions and can easily prioritize heavy workloads daily with above and beyond work ethic.

Areas of Expertise

- UI design and development
- Responsive web design best practices
- Translate design and prototyping to code
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Extensive creative troubleshooting
- Comprehensive quality assurance

Technical Competencies

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Pug(Jade), Stylus, Sitecore, Ember.js, Foundation, Materialize, Bourbon, Neat, Adobe XD, Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Node.js, Word Press, Git, Atlassian Confluence, Atlassian JIRA, Tealium, Quality Assurance, Cross Browser Compatibility, Image Optimization, Microsoft: Access, Word, Powerpoint, Excel

Work Experience

Marketing Front End Developer, Fisher Investments — Camas, WA

Oct 2016 — Present

- Design, develop, and ensure data integrity of all global marketing lead gen web funnels while preserving cross browser compatibility and mobile optimization
- Reduced development and speed-to-market time of a single web funnel from three weeks to two days
- Collaborate with third party vendor teams on development, quality assurance, and front-end flexibility of the Sitecore platform to establish bug free enterprise level web environment
- Participate in creative discussions with digital campaigns and analytics teams on UI design variations with multiple phases of thorough test plans
- Migrated and rebuilt 12 different country corporate websites to updated Sitecore platform

Web Content Specialist, Wacom Technology Corp. — Portland, OR

Jul 2016 — Oct 2016

- Integrated, edited, and proofread web content while maintaining existing templates within style guidelines for the corporate site with Sitecore platform and e-commerce platform Insite
- Partnered with UX designers to create user-friendly and attractive product promotion web pages

Web Development Intern, Mash LLC — Portland, OR

Jun 2016 — Jul 2016

• Developed and converted interface designs from desktop and mobile Sketch mock-ups to live code of an interactive game of Tic, Tac, Toe for internship project

Education

Web Development, Epicodus — Portland, OR
Bachelor of Arts, Asia Studies, University of Washington — Seattle, WA
Associates of Arts, Japanese Language, Lewis and Clark College — Vancouver, WA